She was hired to watch over the kids. But who was going to watch over her?
The Babysitter's Seduction is a drama, thriller, tv
movie film directed by David Burton Morris.
The mother of the family for which Michelle baby-sits dies unexpectedly.
Michelle is asked to take over looking after the children
and is gradually "seduced" by the father.
Michelle Winston, played by Keri Russell.
Bill Bartrand, played by Stephen Collins.
Kate Jacobs, played by Phylicia Rashād.
Frank O'Keefe, played by Tobin Bell.
Paul Richards, played by John D'Aquino.
Alice Winston, played by Linda Kelsey.
The Babysitter’s Seduction is a 1996 American drama television film directed by
David Burton Morris; starring Stephen Collins and Keri Russell.
The film explores themes of lolita, high school, seduction, babysitter, romance.
The tone is emotional and intense.